// Creates the admin user. Remember to start mongod with --auth options to enable authentication.
var db = db.getSiblingDB("interview");
db.createUser(
	{
		user : "interview", 
		pwd : "interview-1517",  // interview-1517
		roles : [ 
			{ 
				role: "dbOwner", 
				db : "interview" 
			}
		]
	}
);

// Creates the user collection specifying the collation.
db.createCollection("user", {
		collation: { 
			locale : "it",
			strength : 1
		} 
});

// Creates the admin user.
db.user.insert({
        "_id" : "interview@aurasphere.co",
        "_class" : "co.aurasphere.interview.server.model.User",
        "authorities" : [
                {
                        "role" : "ROLE_ADMIN",
                        "_class" : "org.springframework.security.core.authority.SimpleGrantedAuthority"
                }
        ],
        "password" : "G2n0QQbKzOx9F8Ve9y2K4bJSMK66yfa", // interview-1517
        "creationTime" : ISODate("2017-11-02T17:33:56.212Z"),
		"enabled" : true
});

// Creates the indexes for the search form.
db.user.createIndex(
	{
		name : 1
	}
);

db.user.createIndex(
	{
		surname : 1
	}
);

// Inserts the technologies into the DB.
db.technology.insertOne({"_id":"Java","_class":"co.aurasphere.interview.server.model.Technology"});

// Inserts the surveys into the DB.
db.survey.insertOne({"_id":"Java Base + Database","_class":"co.aurasphere.interview.server.model.Survey","questions":[{"questionText":"Una classe non puÃ² essere dichiarata...","answers":["Static","Private","Default","Nessuna delle precedenti"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[2]},{"questionText":"Come si puÃ² evitare che una variabile membro diventi serializzata?","answers":["Marcandola private","Marcandola volatile","Marcandola transient","Non Ã¨ possibile"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[2]},{"questionText":"Cos'Ã¨ un instanceof?","answers":["I metodi di un oggetto","Un operatore e parola chiave","Nessuna delle precedenti"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[1]},{"questionText":"Il seguente frammento di codice Java: \u003cpre class=\"prettyprint linenums lang-java\"\u003e class A {\n\n\n public static void main(String [] args) { B b = new A(); } } class B extends A {}\u003c/pre\u003e Quale risultato dÃ ?","answers":["Compile error","Runtime Exception","No error"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[0]},{"questionText":"Il seguente frammento di codice Java:\u003cdiv class=\"code-block\"\u003e\u003cpre class=\"pre-code-block\"\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-primitive\"\u003efloat\u003c/span\u003e a \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e=\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e9\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e/\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e0\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e;\u003c/span\u003e \u003c/pre\u003e\u003c/div\u003e\u003cbr/\u003eQuale risultato dÃ ?","answers":["Compilation error: Divisions must be in a try block","Compilation error: DivideByZeroException","Runtime Exception","No Error: a is NaN"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[2]},{"questionText":"Il seguente frammento di codice Java:\u003cdiv class=\"code-block\"\u003e\u003cpre class=\"pre-code-block\"\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003eclass\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-class-name\"\u003eA\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e{\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e     \u003cspan class=\"code-primitive\"\u003eint\u003c/span\u003e b \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e=\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e1\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e;\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e     \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003epublic\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003estatic\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-primitive\"\u003evoid\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-method-signature-name\"\u003emain\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e(\u003c/span\u003eString\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e[]\u003c/span\u003e args\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e)\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e{\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e             System\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-method\"\u003eout\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-method\"\u003eprintln\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e(\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-string\"\u003e\u0026quot;b is \u0026quot;\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e+\u003c/span\u003e b\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e);\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e        \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e}\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e}\u003c/span\u003e\u003c/pre\u003e\u003c/div\u003e\u003cbr/\u003eQuale risultato dÃ ?","answers":["Compilation error","Runtime Error","Runtime Exception","Output of b is 1"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[0]},{"questionText":"Il seguente frammento di codice Java:\u003cdiv class=\"code-block\"\u003e\u003cpre class=\"pre-code-block\"\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-primitive\"\u003eint\u003c/span\u003e a \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e=\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e3.5\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e;\u003c/span\u003e\u003c/pre\u003e\u003c/div\u003e\u003cbr/\u003eQuale risultato dÃ ?","answers":["Compilation error","Runtime error","a being 3.5","a being 3"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[0]},{"questionText":"Il seguente frammento di codice Java:\u003cdiv class=\"code-block\"\u003e\u003cpre class=\"pre-code-block\"\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-primitive\"\u003eint\u003c/span\u003e k \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e=\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e4\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e;\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-primitive\"\u003eint\u003c/span\u003e n \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e=\u003c/span\u003e k\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e;\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-primitive\"\u003eint\u003c/span\u003e p \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e=\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e1\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e;\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003ewhile\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e(\u003c/span\u003en \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e\u0026gt;\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e0\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e)\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e{\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e    p \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e*=\u003c/span\u003e n\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e;\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e    n\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e--;\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e}\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003eSystem\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-method\"\u003eout\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-method\"\u003eprintln\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e(\u003c/span\u003ek \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e+\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-string\"\u003e\u0026quot;! = \u0026quot;\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e+\u003c/span\u003e p\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e);\u003c/span\u003e\u003c/pre\u003e\u003c/div\u003e\u003cbr/\u003eQuale risultato dÃ ?","answers":["Il frammento di codice compila, ma in esecuzione ciclo all'infinito","Il frammento di codice compila e produce a standard output la stringa \"4! = 24\"","Il frammento di codice non compila, il ciclo while deve essere sostituito da un ciclo for","Nessuna delle precedenti affermazioni Ã¨ corretta"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[1]},{"questionText":"Quale Ã¨ il risultato dell'esecuzione del seguente metodo Java?\u003cdiv class=\"code-block\"\u003e\u003cpre class=\"pre-code-block\"\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003epublic\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003estatic\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-primitive\"\u003eint\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-method-signature-name\"\u003efattoriale\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e(\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-primitive\"\u003eint\u003c/span\u003e n\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e)\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e{\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e     \u003cspan class=\"code-primitive\"\u003eint\u003c/span\u003e p \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e=\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e1\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e;\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e     \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003ewhile\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e(\u003c/span\u003en \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e\u0026gt;\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e0\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e)\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e{\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e         p \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e=\u003c/span\u003e p \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e*\u003c/span\u003e n\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e;\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e         n \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e=\u003c/span\u003e decrementa\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e(\u003c/span\u003en\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e);\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e     \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e}\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e     \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003ereturn\u003c/span\u003e p\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e;\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e}\u003c/span\u003e\u003c/pre\u003e\u003c/div\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e","answers":["il fattoriale di n se n \u003e 0, altrimenti 1","sempre 1, per qualsiasi valore di n","il metodo non termina a causa di un ciclo infinito"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[0]},{"questionText":"Dato il seguente frammento di codice Java:\u003cdiv class=\"code-block\"\u003e\u003cpre class=\"pre-code-block\"\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003epublic\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003eclass\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-class-name\"\u003eTest\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e{\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e     \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003epublic\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003estatic\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-primitive\"\u003evoid\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-method-signature-name\"\u003emain\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e(\u003c/span\u003eString\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e[]\u003c/span\u003e args\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e)\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e{\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e         Integer x \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e=\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003enew\u003c/span\u003e Integer\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e(\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e5\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e);\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e         Integer y \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e=\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003enew\u003c/span\u003e Integer\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e(\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e5\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e);\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e         System\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-method\"\u003eout\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-method\"\u003eprintln\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e(\u003c/span\u003ex \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e==\u003c/span\u003e y\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e);\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e           \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e}\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e}\u003c/span\u003e\u003c/pre\u003e\u003c/div\u003e\u003cbr/\u003eChe cosa restituisce x==y?","answers":["Errore di compilazione","Runtime Exception","True","False"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[3]},{"questionText":"Quali, tra i seguenti frammenti di codice JavaScript, attribuiscono alla variabile  b un valore maggiore di 0, assumendo che i valori di a e c siano rispettivamente 5 e 0?","answers":["\u003cdiv class=\"code-block\"\u003e\u003cpre class=\"pre-code-block\"\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003eif\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e(\u003c/span\u003ea \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e\u0026gt;\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e0\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e)\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e     \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003eif\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e(\u003c/span\u003ec \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e\u0026gt;\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e0\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e)\u003c/span\u003e b \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e=\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e100\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e;\u003c/span\u003e\u003c/pre\u003e\u003c/div\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e","\u003cdiv class=\"code-block\"\u003e\u003cpre class=\"pre-code-block\"\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003eif\u003c/span\u003e ((c \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e\u0026gt;=\u003c/span\u003e a) \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e||\u003c/span\u003e (c \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e\u0026gt;=\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e0\u003c/span\u003e)) b \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e=\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e100\u003c/span\u003e;\u003cbr/\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003eelse\u003c/span\u003e b \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e=\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e-\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e100\u003c/span\u003e;\u003c/pre\u003e\u003c/div\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e","\u003cdiv class=\"code-block\"\u003e\u003cpre class=\"pre-code-block\"\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003eif\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e(\u003c/span\u003ea \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e\u0026gt;\u003c/span\u003e c \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e\u0026amp;\u0026amp;\u003c/span\u003e c \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e\u0026gt;=\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e0\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e)\u003c/span\u003e b \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e=\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e-\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e100\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e;\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003eelse\u003c/span\u003e b \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e=\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e100\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e;\u003c/span\u003e\u003c/pre\u003e\u003c/div\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e","\u003cdiv class=\"code-block\"\u003e\u003cpre class=\"pre-code-block\"\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003eif\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e(\u003c/span\u003ec \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e\u0026gt;\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e0\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e)\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e     \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003eif\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e(\u003c/span\u003ea \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e\u0026gt;\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e4\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e)\u003c/span\u003e b \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e=\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e100\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003eelse\u003c/span\u003e b \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e=\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e-\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e100\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e;\u003c/span\u003e\u003c/pre\u003e\u003c/div\u003e"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[1]},{"questionText":"Dato il seguente foglio di stile esterno:\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cdiv class=\"code-block\"\u003e\u003cpre class=\"pre-code-block\"\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag\"\u003ediv\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-css-class-name\"\u003e.rosso\u003c/span\u003e {\u003cspan class=\"code-css-attribute \"\u003ecolor\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e:\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-css-attribute\"\u003ered\u003c/span\u003e;}\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag\"\u003eli\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-css-class-name\"\u003e.ridotto\u003c/span\u003e {\u003cspan class=\"code-css-attribute\"\u003efont-size\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e:\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-css-number\"\u003e80\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e%\u003c/span\u003e;}\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag\"\u003eli\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-css-class-name\"\u003e.grande\u003c/span\u003e {\u003cspan class=\"code-css-attribute\"\u003efont-size\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e:\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-css-number\"\u003e120\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e%\u003c/span\u003e;}\u003c/pre\u003e\u003c/div\u003e\u003cbr/\u003eIndicare quale dei seguenti frammenti di codice HTML lo utilizzano correttamente:","answers":["\u003cdiv class=\"code-block\"\u003e\u003cpre class=\"pre-code-block\"\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag\"\u003e\u0026lt;ul\u0026gt;\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e     \u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag\"\u003e\u0026lt;li\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag-attribute\"\u003eclass=\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag-attribute-value\"\u003eâ€�rossoâ€�\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag\"\u003e\u0026gt;\u003c/span\u003e primo item \u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag\"\u003e\u0026lt;/li\u0026gt;\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e     \u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag\"\u003e\u0026lt;li\u0026gt;\u003c/span\u003e secondo item \u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag\"\u003e\u0026lt;/li\u0026gt;\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag\"\u003e\u0026lt;/ul\u0026gt;\u003c/span\u003e\u003c/pre\u003e\u003c/div\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e","\u003cdiv class=\"code-block\"\u003e\u003cpre class=\"pre-code-block\"\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag\"\u003e\u0026lt;ul\u0026gt;\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e     \u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag\"\u003e\u0026lt;li\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag-attribute\"\u003eclass=\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag-attribute-value\"\u003eâ€�ridottoâ€�\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag\"\u003e\u0026gt;\u003c/span\u003e primo item \u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag\"\u003e\u0026lt;/li\u0026gt;\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e     \u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag\"\u003e\u0026lt;li\u0026gt;\u003c/span\u003e secondo item \u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag\"\u003e\u0026lt;/li \u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag-attribute\"\u003eclass=\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag-attribute-value\"\u003eâ€�rossoâ€�\u003c/span\u003e\u0026gt;\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag\"\u003e\u0026lt;/ul\u0026gt;\u003c/span\u003e\u003c/pre\u003e\u003c/div\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e","\u003cdiv class=\"code-block\"\u003e\u003cpre class=\"pre-code-block\"\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag\"\u003e\u0026lt;ul\u0026gt;\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e     \u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag\"\u003e\u0026lt;li\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag-attribute\"\u003eclass=\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag-attribute-value\"\u003eâ€�ridottoâ€�\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag\"\u003e\u0026gt;\u003c/span\u003e primo item \u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag\"\u003e\u0026lt;/li\u0026gt;\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e     \u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag\"\u003e\u0026lt;li\u0026gt;\u003c/span\u003e secondo \u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag\"\u003e\u0026lt;div \u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag-attribute\"\u003eclass=\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag-attribute-value\"\u003eâ€�rossoâ€�\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag\"\u003e\u0026gt;\u003c/span\u003e item \u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag\"\u003e\u0026lt;/div\u0026gt;\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag\"\u003e\u0026lt;/li \u0026gt;\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag\"\u003e\u0026lt;/ul\u0026gt;\u003c/span\u003e\u003c/pre\u003e\u003c/div\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e","\u003cdiv class=\"code-block\"\u003e\u003cpre class=\"pre-code-block\"\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag\"\u003e\u0026lt;ul \u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag-attribute\"\u003eclass=\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag-attribute-value\"\u003eâ€�ridottoâ€�\u003c/span\u003e\u0026gt;\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e     \u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag\"\u003e\u0026lt;li\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag-attribute\"\u003eclass=\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag-attribute-value\"\u003eâ€�ridottoâ€�\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag\"\u003e\u0026gt;\u003c/span\u003e primo item \u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag\"\u003e\u0026lt;/li\u0026gt;\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e     \u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag\"\u003e\u0026lt;li\u0026gt;\u003c/span\u003e secondo item \u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag\"\u003e\u0026lt;/li \u0026gt;\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-html-tag\"\u003e\u0026lt;/ul\u0026gt;\u003c/span\u003e\u003c/pre\u003e\u003c/div\u003e"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[2]},{"questionText":"Row is synonymous with the term:","answers":["Record.","relation.","column.","field."],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[0]},{"questionText":"Which of the following is a group of one or more attributes that uniquely identifies a row?","answers":["Key","Determinant","Tuple","Relation"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[0]},{"questionText":"When the values in one or more attributes being used as a foreign key must exist in another set of one or more attributes in another table, we have created a(n):","answers":["transitive dependency.","insertion anomaly.","referential integrity constraint.","normal form."],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[3]},{"questionText":"A key:","answers":["must always be composed of two or more columns.","can only be one column.","identifies a row.","identifies a column."],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[2]},{"questionText":"SQL views can be used to hide:","answers":["columns and rows only.","complicated SQL syntax only.","both of the above can be hidden by an SQL view.","None of the above is correct"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[2]},{"questionText":"In a 1:N relationship, the foreign key is placed in:","answers":["either table without specifying parent and child tables.","the parent table.","the child table.","either the parent table or the child table."],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[2]},{"questionText":"A primary key should be defined as:","answers":["NULL.","NOT NULL.","Either of the above can be used.","None of the above are correct."],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[1]},{"questionText":"A UNION query is which of the following?","answers":["Combines the output from no more than two queries and must include the same number of columns.","Combines the output from no more than two queries and does not include the same number of columns.","Combines the output from multiple queries and must include the same number of columns.","Combines the output from multiple queries and does not include the same number of columns."],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[2]}],"technology":"Java","time":0}	);

db.survey.insertOne({"_id":"Java 8 + Design Patterns","_class":"co.aurasphere.interview.server.model.Survey","questions":[{"questionText":"What is the output?\u003cdiv class=\"code-block\"\u003e\u003cpre class=\"pre-code-block\"\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e2\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003eimport\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan sclass=\"code-static-import\"\u003ejava.util.*\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e;\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e3\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003epublic\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003eclass\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-class-name\"\u003eTest2\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e{\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e4\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e     \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003epublic\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003estatic\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-primitive\"\u003evoid\u003c/span\u003e main\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e(\u003c/span\u003eString a\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e[]){\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e5\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e          Map s \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e=\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003enew\u003c/span\u003e Hashtable\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e();\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e6\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e          s\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-method\"\u003eput\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e(\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003enull\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e,\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003enull\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e);\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e7\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e          System\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-method\"\u003eout\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-method\"\u003eprintln\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e(\u003c/span\u003es\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e);\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e8\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e     \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e}\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e9\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e}\u003c/span\u003e \u003c/pre\u003e\u003c/div\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e","answers":["null","NullPointerException","[null = null]","[]"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[1]},{"questionText":"What is the output?\u003cdiv class=\"code-block\"\u003e\u003cpre class=\"pre-code-block\"\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e1\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003eimport\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-static-import\"\u003ejava.util.*\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e;\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e2\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003epublic\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003eclass\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-class-name\"\u003eTest4\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e{\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e3\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e     \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003epublic\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003estatic\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-primitive\"\u003evoid\u003c/span\u003e main\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e(\u003c/span\u003eString a\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e[]){\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e4\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e         Map s \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e=\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003enew\u003c/span\u003e LinkedHashMap\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e();\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e5\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e         s\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-method\"\u003eput\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e(\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-string\"\u003e\u0026quot;1\u0026quot;\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e,\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-string\"\u003e\u0026quot;one\u0026quot;\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e);\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e6\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e         s\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-method\"\u003eput\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e(\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-string\"\u003e\u0026quot;3\u0026quot;\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e,\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-string\"\u003e\u0026quot;three\u0026quot;\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e);\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e7\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e         s\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-method\"\u003eput\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e(\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-string\"\u003e\u0026quot;2\u0026quot;\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e,\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-string\"\u003e\u0026quot;two\u0026quot;\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e);\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e8\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e         System\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-method\"\u003eout\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-method\"\u003eprintln\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e(\u003c/span\u003es\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e);\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e9\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e     \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e}\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e10\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e}\u003c/span\u003e \u003c/pre\u003e\u003c/div\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e","answers":["[1=one,2=two,3=three]","NullPointerException","[1=one,3=three,2=two]","[]"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[2]},{"questionText":"How will you synchronize below given HashMap object?\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cdiv class=\"code-block\"\u003e\u003cpre class=\"pre-code-block\"\u003eHashMap hashmap = \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003enew\u003c/span\u003e HashMap();\u003c/pre\u003e\u003c/div\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e","answers":["Collections.synchronized(hashmap);","Map.synchronizedMap(hashmap);","Collections.synchronizedMap(hashmap);","Map.synchronized(hashmap);"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[2]},{"questionText":"Which is a valid declaration within an interface?","answers":["protected short stop = 23;","public Boolean demo(long bow);","final void demo(short stop);","static char demo(double duty);"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[1]},{"questionText":"Can an abstract class define both abstract methods and non-abstract methods?","answers":["No, it must have all one or the other.","Yes, but the child classes do not inherit the abstract methods.","No, it must have all abstract methods.","Yes, the child classes inherit both."],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[3]},{"questionText":"For a given code snippet\u003cdiv class=\"code-block\"\u003e\u003cpre class=\"pre-code-block\"\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e1\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003epublic\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003eclass\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-class-name\"\u003eConstructor\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e{\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e2\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e        \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003epublic\u003c/span\u003e Constructor \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e(\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-primitive\"\u003eint\u003c/span\u003e x\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e,\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-primitive\"\u003eint\u003c/span\u003e y\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e,\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-primitive\"\u003eint\u003c/span\u003e z\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e)\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e3\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e        \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e{}\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e4\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e}\u003c/span\u003e \u003c/pre\u003e\u003c/div\u003e\u003cbr/\u003eWhich of the following is considered as overloaded constructor?","answers":["public void Constructor(int x, int y, byte z){}","private Object Constructor() {}","Constructor() {}","protected int Constructor(){}"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[2]},{"questionText":"Lambda expressions in Java 8 are based on...","answers":["Procedural programming","Functional programming","Data programming","All"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[1]},{"questionText":"How many methods are there in functional interface in Java 8?","answers":["0","1","2","3"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[1]},{"questionText":"Stream operations in Java 8 can be divided into...","answers":["Terminal types","Intermediate types","All","None"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[2]},{"questionText":"Which of these represents a process that accepts one argument and produces a result in Java 8?","answers":["Function","Process","Method","JavaFunctions"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[0]},{"questionText":"In Java 8 Function is...","answers":["Class","Interface","Lambda Expression","Object"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[1]},{"questionText":"What can help us in avoiding NullPointerExceptions and null checks in Java 8?","answers":["Optional","Required","NotNull","NotRequired"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[0]},{"questionText":"Code before Java 8 essentially used to be...","answers":["Declarative","Imperative","Subjective","None"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[1]},{"questionText":"In Java 8, R apply(T t) is a method of...","answers":["Function","Process","Predicate","None"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[0]},{"questionText":"Which of these does Stream.map() operates on?","answers":["Class","Interface","Predicate","Function"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[3]},{"questionText":"Which method can be used to check null on an Optional variable in Java 8?","answers":["isPresent()","isNullable()","isPresentable()","isNotNull()"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[0]},{"questionText":"Which of these does forEach() operates on?","answers":["Methods","Consumer","Producer","Producer"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[1]},{"questionText":"\"map\" and \"filter\" are...","answers":["Parallel operations","Intermediate operations","Terminal operations","Initial operations"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[1]},{"questionText":"Lambda expressions used in Streams should be...","answers":["Stateful","Stateless","Either stateful or stateless","Stateful only if they are thread-safe"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[1]},{"questionText":"Which design pattern creates a complex object using simple objects and using a step by step approach?","answers":["Facade Pattern","Builder pattern","Factory pattern","Iterator Pattern"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[1]},{"questionText":"Adapter pattern is also called __________.","answers":["Decorator pattern","Template pattern","Wrapper pattern","State pattern"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[2]},{"questionText":"To make user use same instance of class across application we should use __________.","answers":["Iterator Pattern","Command Pattern","Facade Pattern","Singleton Pattern"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[3]},{"questionText":"Which of the following is true for facade pattern?","answers":["The facade class provides basic, simplified services to clients by taking upon itself the job of dealing with a complex sub-system.","The Facade pattern eases interaction between a client and a sub-system of suppliers by providing a simpler interface to the sub-system","All of the above","Sub-systems may be complex, but often clients only need basic services that can be supplied through a simple interface."],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[2]}],"technology":"Java","time":0});

db.survey.insertOne({"_id":"Java Middle Senior","_class":"co.aurasphere.interview.server.model.Survey","questions":[{"questionText":"Java EE, the Java Enterprise Edition, is...","answers":["an improved version of the Java Standard Edition for business professionals","a development environment, designed for creating enterprise applications","a platform for enterprise class level, distributed applications","a replacement of the Java Virtual Machine for running internet applications"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[2]},{"questionText":"Container services are configured via...","answers":["special configuration methods in Java Access Beans","deployment descriptors","resource property files","application server administration configuration"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[1]},{"questionText":"Which of the following is NOT true?","answers":["Java EE applications are based on 4 phases: development, assembly, deployment, administration","Java EE applications are autonomic self-managing, self-healing, self-protecting enterprise applications","Java EE applications are split up in multiple tiers: client tier, web tier, EJB tier and integration tier","Java EE applications are typically a combination of application clients, web components and EJBs"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[1]},{"questionText":"Which elements are not part of the Java EE specification? (2 answers)","answers":["applets","Java Mail","portlets","Unified Expression Language"],"type":"MULTIPLE_ANSWERS","correctAnswers":[0,2]},{"questionText":"Which of the following descriptions of a Java EE web application are correct? (2 answers)","answers":["A Java EE web application may contain servlets and applets","A Java EE web application may contain servlets and EJBs","A Java EE web application may contain JavaServer Pages and JavaBeans","A Java EE web application must contain JavaServer Pages and applets"],"type":"MULTIPLE_ANSWERS","correctAnswers":[0,2]},{"questionText":"JavaServer Faces...","answers":["are a replacement of JavaServer Pages","are used as a facade for servlets and JavaServer Pages","is an MVC based web framework","is the new name of the Struts framework"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[2]},{"questionText":"Enterprise Java Beans...","answers":["must be deployed in a Java EE web container","implement server side business components","are used as a replacement of a relational database","are necessary for the integration with enterprise services"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[1]},{"questionText":"Java Messaging Service (JMS)...","answers":["allows messages to participate in a distributed transaction","enables the synchronous exchange of messages","is necessary for sending and receiving e-mails","is a non-standard Java EE feature of IBM WebSphere MQ"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[0]},{"questionText":"The best way to access a database from a standard Java EE application is...","answers":["based on a dynamic lookup of a datasource via JNDI (Java Naming and Directory Interface)","using a JDBC DriverManager to optimize the connection to the database","working with static SQL statements via SQLJ","developing a customised persistency framework, based on JDBC type 1 drivers"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[0]},{"questionText":"Which quote illustrates best the support of web services in Java EE?","answers":["Java EE application servers contain a specific web services container to interact with other web services","Java EE provides the required XML APIs and tools in order to quickly and effectively design, develop, test and deploy web services","The web services support is part of the Java SE, and as such is available in Java EE too.","The Java EE server provides special deployment descriptors for web services"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[1]},{"questionText":"The use of a relational database in a Java EE environment is supported best by...","answers":["Bean Managed Persistent Enterprise Entity Beans","POJO Entities with annotations and controlled by an implementation of the Java Persistence Architecture","Container Managed Transactional beans with direct JDBC access","POJO beans and the specification of SQL in the EJB deployment descriptor"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[1]},{"questionText":"The EJB specification architecture defines... (2 correct answers)","answers":["Client side security and encryption","Distributed object components","Relational database components","Transactional components"],"type":"MULTIPLE_ANSWERS","correctAnswers":[1,3]},{"questionText":"What type of enterprise bean is used to embody application processing state information?","answers":["javax.ejb.EnterpriseBean","javax.ejb.MessageBean","javax.ejb.SessionBean","javax.ejb.EntityBean"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[2]},{"questionText":"A Java EE Enterprise Application Archive (EAR) contains typically...","answers":["client modules, web modules, EJB modules and resource adapters","EJB modules and the associated deployment descriptors","web modules and the associated deployment descriptors","all the deployment descriptors for the enterprise modules"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[0]},{"questionText":"Which quote about Java EE transaction management is NOT correct?","answers":["Java EE transaction management supports distributed transactions with 2-phase commit","Java EE transaction management supports the Web services - Transaction specification","Java EE transaction management supports the flat transaction model","Java EE transaction management implies by default auto commit"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[1]},{"questionText":"Security in Java EE... (2 answers)","answers":["is provided by the Java EE containers","requires the Java Authentication and Authorisation Service (JAAS) on the web tier","is implemented as single sign-on feature, relying on an LDAP server","is based on realms, users, groups and roles"],"type":"MULTIPLE_ANSWERS","correctAnswers":[0,3]},{"questionText":"Which pattern is NOT defined as a Java EE pattern (or Java EE blueprint)?","answers":["Business Delegate","Decorator","Service to Worker","Data Access Object"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[1]},{"questionText":"Which is true? (Choose all that apply.)","answers":["\"X extends Y\" is correct if and only if X is a class and Y is an interface","\"X extends Y\" is correct if and only if X is an interface and Y is a class","\"X extends Y\" is correct if X and Y are either both classes or both interfaces","\"X extends Y\" is correct for all combinations of X and Y being classes and/or interfaces"],"type":"MULTIPLE_ANSWERS","correctAnswers":[2]},{"questionText":"Given two files:\u003cdiv class=\"code-block\"\u003e\u003cpre class=\"pre-code-block\"\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e1\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003epackage\u003c/span\u003e pkgA\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e;\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e2\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003epublic\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003eclass\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-class-name\"\u003eFoo\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e{\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e3\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e     \u003cspan class=\"code-primitive\"\u003eint\u003c/span\u003e a \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e=\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number\"\u003e5\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e;\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e4\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e     \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003eprotected\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-primitive\"\u003eint\u003c/span\u003e b \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e=\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number\"\u003e6\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e;\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e5\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e     \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003epublic\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-primitive\"\u003eint\u003c/span\u003e c \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e=\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number\"\u003e7\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e;\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e6\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e}\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e                                               \u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e3\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003epackage\u003c/span\u003e pkgB\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e;\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e4\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003eimport\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-static-import\"\u003epkgA.*\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e;\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e5\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003epublic\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003eclass\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-class-name\"\u003eBaz\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e{\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e6\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e     \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003epublic\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003estatic\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-primitive\"\u003evoid\u003c/span\u003e main\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e(\u003c/span\u003eString\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e[]\u003c/span\u003e args\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e)\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e{\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e7\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e         Foo f \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e=\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003enew\u003c/span\u003e Foo\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e();\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e8\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e         System\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-method\"\u003eout\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-method\"\u003eprint\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e(\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-string\"\u003e\u0026quot; \u0026quot;\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e+\u003c/span\u003e f\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-method\"\u003ea\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e);\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e9\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e         System\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-method\"\u003eout\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-method\"\u003eprint\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e(\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-string\"\u003e\u0026quot; \u0026quot;\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e+\u003c/span\u003e f\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-method\"\u003eb\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e);\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e10\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e         System\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-method\"\u003eout\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-method\"\u003eprint\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e(\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-string\"\u003e\u0026quot; \u0026quot;\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e+\u003c/span\u003e f\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-method\"\u003ec\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e);\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e11\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e     \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e}\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number-or-line-number\"\u003e12\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e}\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003c/pre\u003e\u003c/div\u003e\u003cbr/\u003eWhat is the result? (Choose all that apply.)","answers":["5 6 7","5 followed by an exception","Compilation fails with an error on line 7","Compilation fails with an error on line 8","Compilation fails with an error on line 9","Compilation fails with an error on line 10"],"type":"MULTIPLE_ANSWERS","correctAnswers":[3,4]},{"questionText":"Given: \u003cdiv class=\"code-block\"\u003e\u003cpre class=\"pre-code-block\"\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003epublic\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003eabstract\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003einterface\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-class-name\"\u003eFrobnicate\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e{\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e     \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003epublic\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-primitive\"\u003evoid\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-method-signature-name\"\u003etwiddle\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e(\u003c/span\u003eString s\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e);\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e}\u003c/span\u003e \u003c/pre\u003e\u003c/div\u003e\u003cbr/\u003eWhich is a correct class? (Choose all that apply.)","answers":["\u003cdiv class=\"code-block\"\u003e\u003cpre class=\"pre-code-block\"\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003epublic\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003eabstract\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003eclass\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-class-name\"\u003eFrob\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003eimplements\u003c/span\u003e Frobnicate \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e{\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e     \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003epublic\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003eabstract\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-primitive\"\u003evoid\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-method-signature-name\"\u003etwiddle\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e(\u003c/span\u003eString s\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e)\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e{}\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e}\u003c/span\u003e \u003c/pre\u003e\u003c/div\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e","\u003cdiv class=\"code-block\"\u003e\u003cpre class=\"pre-code-block\"\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003epublic\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003eabstract\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003eclass\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-class-name\"\u003eFrob\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003eimplements\u003c/span\u003e Frobnicate \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e{}\u003c/span\u003e \u003c/pre\u003e\u003c/div\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e","\u003cdiv class=\"code-block\"\u003e\u003cpre class=\"pre-code-block\"\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003epublic\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003eclass\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-class-name\"\u003eFrob\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003eextends\u003c/span\u003e Frobnicate \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e{\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e     \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003epublic\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-primitive\"\u003evoid\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-method-signature-name\"\u003etwiddle\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e(\u003c/span\u003eInteger i\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e)\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e{}\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e}\u003c/span\u003e \u003c/pre\u003e\u003c/div\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e","\u003cdiv class=\"code-block\"\u003e\u003cpre class=\"pre-code-block\"\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003epublic\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003eclass\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-class-name\"\u003eFrob\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003eimplements\u003c/span\u003e Frobnicate \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e{\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e     \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003epublic\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-primitive\"\u003evoid\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-method-signature-name\"\u003etwiddle\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e(\u003c/span\u003eInteger i\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e)\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e{}\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e}\u003c/span\u003e \u003c/pre\u003e\u003c/div\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e","\u003cdiv class=\"code-block\"\u003e\u003cpre class=\"pre-code-block\"\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003epublic\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003eclass\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-class-name\"\u003eFrob\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003eimplements\u003c/span\u003e Frobnicate \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e{\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e     \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003epublic\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-primitive\"\u003evoid\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-method-signature-name\"\u003etwiddle\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e(\u003c/span\u003eString i\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e)\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e{}\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e     \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003epublic\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-primitive\"\u003evoid\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-method-signature-name\"\u003etwiddle\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e(\u003c/span\u003eInteger s\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e)\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e{}\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e}\u003c/span\u003e \u003c/pre\u003e\u003c/div\u003e"],"type":"MULTIPLE_ANSWERS","correctAnswers":[1]},{"questionText":"Given the following:\u003cdiv class=\"code-block\"\u003e\u003cpre class=\"pre-code-block\"\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number\"\u003e1\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003eclass\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-class-name\"\u003eX\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e{\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-primitive\"\u003evoid\u003c/span\u003e do1\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e()\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e{\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e}\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e}\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number\"\u003e2\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003eclass\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-class-name\"\u003eY\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003eextends\u003c/span\u003e X \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e{\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-primitive\"\u003evoid\u003c/span\u003e do2\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e()\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e{\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e}\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e}\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number\"\u003e3\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number\"\u003e4\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003eclass\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-class-name\"\u003eChrome\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e{\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number\"\u003e5\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e     \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003epublic\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003estatic\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-primitive\"\u003evoid\u003c/span\u003e main\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e(\u003c/span\u003eString \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e[]\u003c/span\u003e args\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e)\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e{\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number\"\u003e6\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e         X x1 \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e=\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003enew\u003c/span\u003e X\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e();\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number\"\u003e7\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e         X x2 \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e=\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003enew\u003c/span\u003e Y\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e();\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number\"\u003e8\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e         Y y1 \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e=\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-keyword\"\u003enew\u003c/span\u003e Y\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e();\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number\"\u003e9\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e         \u003cspan class=\"code-comment\"\u003e// insert code here\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number\"\u003e10\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e    \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e}\u003c/span\u003e\u003cbr/\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-literal-or-line-number\"\u003e11\u003c/span\u003e\u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e.\u003c/span\u003e \u003cspan class=\"code-default-color\"\u003e}\u003c/span\u003e \u003c/pre\u003e\u003c/div\u003e\u003cbr/\u003eWhich, inserted at line 9, will compile? (Choose all that apply.)","answers":["x2.do2();","(Y)x2.do2();","((Y)x2).do2();","None of the above statements will compile"],"type":"MULTIPLE_ANSWERS","correctAnswers":[2]}],"technology":"Java","time":0});

db.survey.insertOne({"_id":"Spring","_class":"co.aurasphere.interview.server.model.Survey","questions":[{"questionText":"The default scope of bean is 'singleton'.","answers":["True","False"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[0]},{"questionText":"What are the types of injection supported by Spring?","answers":["Constructor Injection, Setter Injection and Interface Injection","Constructor Injection only.","Constructor Injection, Setter Injection before 2.0 and Interface Injection with 2.0 and above version","Constructor Injection and Setter Injection"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[3]},{"questionText":"Which event is published when context is initialized?","answers":["ContextReadyEvent","ContextInitializedEvent","ContextRefreshedEvent","ContextStartedEvent"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[2]},{"questionText":"Spring event mechanism is based on the standard:","answers":["Observer Design Pattern","Mediator Design Pattern","Factory Design Pattern"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[0]},{"questionText":"What is dependency injection?","answers":["A design pattern where dependent objects are defined in an xml for easy maintainability.","This is a design pattern whereby dependent objects are passed into an object from the outside at the time application is initialized.","A unique feature of spring which allows object to be injected at the time of compilation."],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[1]},{"questionText":"A bean must have id attribute in beans configuration file.","answers":["True","False"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[1]},{"questionText":"What BeanPostProcessor does?","answers":["It processes beans once a bean is initialized.","It defines callback methods that you can implement to provide your own instantiation logic, dependency-resolution logic etc.","It processes beans once a bean is loaded.","It processes beans once a bean exits."],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[1]},{"questionText":"What is true about \u003clist\u003e collection configuration elements?","answers":["This helps in wiring a list of values, allowing duplicates.","This helps in wiring a list of values but without any duplicates.","This can be used to inject a collection of name-value pairs where name and value can be of any type.","This can be used to inject a collection of name-value pairs where the name and value are both Strings."],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[0]},{"questionText":"If a bean is scoped to HTTP request, scope is:","answers":["session","global-session","prototype","request"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[3]},{"questionText":"Which programming technique allows programmers to modularize crosscutting concerns, or behavior?","answers":["Spring AOP","Spring DAO","Spring ORM","Spring Roo"],"type":"SINGLE_ANSWER","correctAnswers":[0]}],"technology":"Java","time":0});